<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ClassTime</string>
    
    <!-- Main Screen -->
    <string name="week_view">Week View</string>
    <string name="day_view">Day View</string>
    <string name="import_schedule">Import Schedule</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    
    <!-- Course Related -->
    <string name="course_name">Course Name</string>
    <string name="teacher">Teacher</string>
    <string name="classroom">Classroom</string>
    <string name="week_range">Week Range</string>
    <string name="add_course">Add Course</string>
    <string name="edit_course">Edit Course</string>
    <string name="delete_course">Delete Course</string>
    
    <!-- Notification Related -->
    <string name="class_reminder">Class Reminder</string>
    <string name="reminder_channel_name">Course Reminder</string>
    <string name="reminder_channel_description">Show upcoming class reminders</string>
    
    <!-- General -->
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    
    <!-- Disclaimer -->
    <string name="disclaimer_title">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_subtitle">View app disclaimer</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_acknowledge">I Acknowledge</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_agree">I have read and agree</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_disagree">Disagree and Exit</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_content">━━━━ ClassTime - Disclaimer ━━━━\n\n【IMPORTANT】Please read this statement carefully. Continuing to use this app means you fully understand and agree to accept all the following terms.\n\n━━━━ 1. App Introduction and Developer Identity ━━━━\n\n1.1 App Introduction\nThis app \"ClassTime\" (时课) is a campus schedule management application that supports integration with educational administration systems from over 100 universities across China, covering mainstream systems such as Zhengfang (正方), Shuwei (树维), Qiangzhi (强智), Qingguo (青果), URP, Jinzhi (金智), and custom systems. The app provides core features including intelligent schedule import, automatic updates, course reminders, and data backup.\n\n1.2 Developer Identity\nThis app is independently developed by an individual student as a practice project for learning modern Android development technologies such as Kotlin, Jetpack Compose, Room Database, etc. It does not have commercial operation qualifications and is a non-commercial product.\n\n1.3 Scope of Use\nThis app is only for the following legitimate purposes:\n• Personal learning and technical research\n• Personal course time management and schedule planning\n• Non-commercial academic exchange and technical sharing\n• Teaching and research activity assistance tools\n\n1.4 Prohibited Behaviors\nIt is strictly prohibited to use this app for any of the following behaviors:\n✗ Any form of commercial use, profit-making activities, or commercial operations\n✗ Activities that violate national laws, regulations, or industry standards\n✗ Activities that violate school or educational institution regulations\n✗ Attacking, cracking, reverse engineering, or malicious exploitation of educational administration systems\n✗ Batch crawling, reselling, distributing, or commercial exploitation of others\' schedule data\n✗ Using others\' account information or identity credentials without authorization\n✗ Any behavior that may interfere with or disrupt the normal operation of educational administration systems\n\n━━━━ 2. Unofficial Statement and Intellectual Property ━━━━\n\n2.1 Independent Development Project\nThis app is independently developed and has no affiliation, cooperation, authorization, or endorsement relationship with the following institutions:\n• Any school, educational institution, and its educational administration system\n• Any third-party website or service provider\n• Any commercial organization or official institution\n\n2.2 Trademarks and Logos\nThe intellectual property rights of school names, educational administration system names, logos, and other trademarks and logos involved in the app belong to their original rights holders. This app only refers to these names in configuration files to implement technical functions and does not represent any form of association or authorization.\n\n2.3 Open Source Components Statement\nThis app uses the following main open source components:\n• Kotlin (Apache 2.0)\n• Jetpack Compose (Apache 2.0)\n• Room Database (Apache 2.0)\n• OkHttp (Apache 2.0)\n• Jsoup (MIT License)\nEach component complies with its respective open source license requirements.\n\n━━━━ 3. Privacy Protection and Data Security ━━━━\n\n3.1 Data Storage Principles\n✓ Local storage: All data is only stored locally on your device\n✓ No cloud upload: No data collection, upload, or synchronization to remote servers\n✓ No account system: The app itself does not require account registration\n✓ No data analysis: No statistics, analysis, or advertising SDKs are integrated\n\n3.2 Sensitive Data Encryption\nThis app adopts the following security measures:\n• Cookies are encrypted using AES-256-GCM algorithm (EncryptedSharedPreferences)\n• Schedule data is stored in a local SQLite database (Room)\n• Cookies are set to automatically expire after 24 hours\n• WebView is configured with security policies, prohibiting file access and mixed content\n\n3.3 Your Data Includes\nWhen using the import function, the following data will be stored locally on your device:\n• Cookie credentials used to log in to the educational administration system (encrypted)\n• Schedule data obtained from the educational administration system (course names, teachers, classrooms, times, etc.)\n• Course information you manually add or edit\n• Your semester configuration and class time settings\n• Exported ICS calendar files and JSON backup files\n\n3.4 Data Security Risks\n⚠️ You need to understand and assume the following risks:\n• Device loss, theft, or access by others may lead to data leakage\n• System vulnerabilities and malware may lead to local data theft\n• Uninstalling the app or clearing data will permanently delete all local data\n• Cookie expiration or invalidation may require re-login\n\n3.5 Data Management Recommendations\nIt is recommended that you take the following measures to protect data security:\n✓ Set a device lock screen password\n✓ Regularly export and back up schedule data (Settings → Data Management → Export JSON)\n✓ Do not use this app on public devices\n✓ Regularly check and clean expired cookies\n\n━━━━ 4. Network Services and WebView Usage ━━━━\n\n4.1 WebView Login Mechanism\nThis app uses Android WebView component to load the school educational administration system login page:\n• You need to manually enter your account and password in WebView\n• The app automatically extracts Cookie credentials after successful login\n• Cookies are used for subsequent HTTP requests to obtain schedule data\n• The app will not actively record or upload your account password\n\n4.2 Network Request Description\nThis app will initiate the following network requests:\n• Access the school educational administration system login page (user-initiated)\n• Request schedule data interface (carrying Cookie authentication)\n• Parse JSON or HTML format schedule data\n\n4.3 Third-party Website Risks\n⚠️ Using WebView and network requests poses the following risks:\n• The security of the educational administration system is the responsibility of the school and is not related to this app\n• Network transmission may be subject to man-in-the-middle attacks (HTTPS is recommended)\n• The educational administration system may change interfaces, causing the import function to fail\n• The educational administration system may ban IPs or accounts with frequent requests\n\n4.4 Compliance Use Responsibility\nYou should ensure:\n✓ Only use your own account to log in to the educational administration system\n✓ Do not frequently request to cause server pressure\n✓ Comply with school regulations on the use of the educational administration system\n✓ Do not attempt to bypass security restrictions or attack the educational administration system\n\n━━━━ 5. System Permission Description ━━━━\n\nThis app applies for the following Android system permissions, used as follows:\n\n【Network Permissions】\n• INTERNET: Access educational administration system web pages and request schedule data\n• ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE: Detect network connection status\n\n【Notification Permissions】\n• POST_NOTIFICATIONS: Send class reminder notifications (Android 13+)\n• USE_FULL_SCREEN_INTENT: Display full-screen reminder notifications\n• VIBRATE: Notification vibration feedback\n\n【Exact Alarm Permissions】\n• SCHEDULE_EXACT_ALARM: Precisely schedule course reminder times (Android 12+)\n• USE_EXACT_ALARM: Use exact alarm function\n\n【Background Running Permissions】\n• FOREGROUND_SERVICE: Run foreground service to ensure timely reminder delivery\n• FOREGROUND_SERVICE_DATA_SYNC: Foreground service type declaration\n• WAKE_LOCK: Wake up device to send reminders\n• RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED: Automatically reschedule reminder tasks after boot\n\n【File Access Permissions】\n• READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE: Read imported backup files (Android 12 and below)\n• WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE: Export ICS calendar and JSON backup (Android 9 and below)\n\n⚠️ Permission Risk Tips:\n• Network permissions may be maliciously used to upload data (this app promises not to upload)\n• Background running permissions will consume battery (can be turned off in settings)\n• File permissions may access other app data (this app only accesses export directory)\n\n━━━━ 6. Notification Reminder Service Description ━━━━\n\n6.1 Reminder Mechanism\nThis app uses WorkManager to schedule course reminders:\n• Automatically calculate reminder times based on schedule and class times\n• Send notifications N minutes in advance (configurable)\n• Notification content includes course name, classroom, teacher, and other information\n\n6.2 Background Running and Battery Optimization\nTo ensure timely reminder delivery, the app may:\n• Apply to be added to the battery optimization whitelist\n• Run foreground service to stay active\n• Keep WorkManager tasks in the background\n\n⚠️ This may lead to:\n• Increased battery consumption (can be turned off in settings)\n• Reminder failure after system kills process (restart app to recover)\n• Some vendor ROMs may restrict background running\n\n6.3 No Delivery Guarantee\nDue to Android system restrictions and vendor customization, this app cannot guarantee 100% timely reminder delivery. Influencing factors include but are not limited to:\n• System Doze mode and app standby\n• Vendor custom power-saving strategies\n• User manually cleans background\n• Insufficient device storage space\n• System version compatibility issues\n\n━━━━ 7. Data Export and Backup Function ━━━━\n\n7.1 Supported Export Formats\n• ICS calendar format: Can be imported into system calendar, Google Calendar, etc.\n• JSON format: App-specific format, can be used for backup and recovery\n\n7.2 Export File Storage Location\n• Android 10+: App-specific directory (/Android/data/com.wind.ggbond.classtime/)\n• Android 9 and below: External storage public directory (/Documents/)\n\n7.3 Export Data Risks\n⚠️ Exported files contain your schedule information, please keep them properly:\n• Do not share with untrusted people\n• Do not upload to public cloud storage\n• Files will not be automatically deleted when the app is deleted\n\n━━━━ 8. System Compatibility and Known Issues ━━━━\n\n8.1 Supported System Versions\n• Minimum version: Android 8.0 (API 26)\n• Target version: Android 14 (API 34)\n• Recommended version: Android 10 and above\n\n8.2 Known Compatibility Issues\n• Android 14+: Need to manually grant full-screen notification permission\n• Xiaomi/Huawei and other custom ROMs: Need to manually set background permissions and auto-start\n• Android 8-9: File export path may be different\n• Some educational administration systems may not be compatible with WebView login\n\n8.3 Function Limitations\n• Dynamic Island function requires Xiaomi HyperOS system support (not yet implemented)\n• Month view function is not yet developed\n• Does not support multiple accounts logging in at the same time\n• Does not support course conflict detection\n\n━━━━ 9. Limitation of Liability and Disclaimer ━━━━\n\n9.1 No Warranty\nThis app is provided on an \"as is\" and \"as available\" basis, without any express or implied warranties, including but not limited to:\n✗ Merchantability warranty\n✗ Fitness for a particular purpose warranty\n✗ Non-infringement warranty\n✗ Error-free operation warranty\n✗ Data accuracy warranty\n\n9.2 Limitation of Liability\nTo the maximum extent permitted by law, the developer is not liable for the following situations:\n• Data loss, corruption, or leakage\n• App crash, lag, or unavailability\n• Late arrival or absence due to undelivered reminders\n• Cookie invalidation requiring re-login\n• Educational administration system banning account\n• Issues with third-party websites or services\n• Device damage or system failure\n• Any direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive, or consequential damages\n\n9.3 No Legal Liability\nIf you violate laws and regulations, school regulations, or this statement when using this app, you shall bear all legal responsibilities arising therefrom, and it has nothing to do with the developer.\n\n9.4 Third-party Responsibility\nThe behavior or issues of educational administration systems, network service providers, device manufacturers, operating system developers, and other third parties shall be borne by themselves and have nothing to do with this app.\n\n━━━━ 10. Special Tips for Minors ━━━━\n\nIf you are under 18 years old, you should:\n✓ Obtain clear consent from your guardian before using this app\n✓ Use under the guidance of your guardian\n✓ Do not enter personal information unrelated to learning\n\nGuardians should:\n✓ Understand the functions and risks of the app\n✓ Supervise the use behavior of minors\n✓ Educate minors to protect personal information security\n\n━━━━ 11. Security Recommendations and Best Practices ━━━━\n\nTo use this app more securely, it is recommended that you:\n\n【Account Security】\n✓ Only log in to your own educational administration system account in this app\n✓ Do not use others\' accounts or shared accounts\n✓ Regularly change educational administration system password\n✓ Do not log in under public Wi-Fi\n\n【Data Security】\n✓ Set device lock screen password or biometric recognition\n✓ Regularly back up schedule data (export JSON)\n✓ Do not screenshot or share pages with personal information\n✓ Export data before uninstalling the app\n\n【Permission Management】\n✓ Only grant necessary permissions to the app\n✓ Can refuse notification permission if reminder function is not needed\n✓ Regularly check app permission settings\n\n【Compliance Use】\n✓ Comply with school regulations on the use of the educational administration system\n✓ Do not frequently refresh schedule data\n✓ Do not attempt to access non-personal schedules\n✓ Report security vulnerabilities in a timely manner\n\n━━━━ 12. Problem Feedback and Open Source Statement ━━━━\n\n12.1 Problem Feedback\nIf you encounter problems or discover security vulnerabilities, you can:\n• Check the contact information through the \"About\" page in the app (if available)\n• Submit an Issue on the app\'s open source code repository (if open source)\n\n12.2 Developer Statement\nAs a student, the developer:\n• Cannot guarantee timely response and problem fixes\n• Does not provide technical support and after-sales service\n• May stop maintenance or updates at any time\n• Does not promise to add new features or adapt to new systems\n\n12.3 App Updates\n• The app may be updated irregularly, and update content may include function changes\n• Updates may fix known issues or introduce new issues\n• Users decide whether to update, it is recommended to back up data before updating\n\n━━━━ 13. Legal Terms and Dispute Resolution ━━━━\n\n13.1 Applicable Law\nThe establishment, effectiveness, interpretation, execution, and dispute resolution of this disclaimer are subject to the laws and regulations of the mainland of the People\'s Republic of China. For matters not stipulated by laws and regulations, industry practices and academic norms shall be referred to.\n\n13.2 Dispute Resolution\nDisputes arising from this app shall be resolved through friendly negotiation first; if negotiation fails, either party may file a lawsuit with a people\'s court with jurisdiction over the developer\'s location.\n\n13.3 Clause Independence\nIf any clause of this statement is deemed invalid or unenforceable, it does not affect the validity of other clauses.\n\n13.4 Complete Agreement\nThis disclaimer constitutes the complete agreement between you and the developer regarding the use of this app, superseding any prior oral or written agreements.\n\n━━━━ 14. Statement Changes and Effectiveness ━━━━\n\n14.1 Right to Change\nThe developer reserves the right to modify and update this disclaimer at any time without separate notice.\n\n14.2 Change Notice\nAfter the statement is changed, the new version will:\n• Be updated in \"Settings - Disclaimer\" in the app\n• Be mentioned in the app update instructions (if there are significant changes)\n• Take effect immediately upon release\n\n14.3 Continued Use Deemed Acceptance\nYour continued use of this app after the statement is changed is deemed to have read, understood, and agreed to accept the changed content. If you do not agree with the changed content, please stop using and uninstall this app immediately.\n\n━━━━ 15. Final Statement ━━━━\n\n✓ By clicking \"I have read and agree\" or continuing to use this app, you indicate that you have read, fully understood, and voluntarily accepted all the terms of this disclaimer.\n\n✓ You confirm that you have full civil capacity and can independently bear the legal responsibilities of using this app; if you are a minor, you have obtained guardian consent.\n\n✓ You understand that this app is a student personal learning project and may have defects and risks, and you voluntarily assume the risks of use.\n\n✓ You promise to use this app legally, compliantly, and reasonably, and not for any illegal or infringing behavior.\n\n✗ If you do not agree with any terms of this statement, please stop using and uninstall this app immediately.\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━\n\nLast updated: January 2025\nVersion: v3.0\n\nClassTime (时课) - Campus Schedule Management App\nSupports 100+ Universities | Intelligent Import | Auto Update\nFor learning and communication only | Commercial use prohibited\n\n━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━━</string>
</resources>







